Inventory of the Donald S. Rothchild papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Research materials, 1923-1983
  - Judiciary, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 150: 6-7)
  - Miscellaneous Africa, 1970 (Box-folder 150: 8)
  - Zambia: Asians, 1969 (Box-folder 151: 1)
  - Uganda: Asians, 1971-1983 (Box-folder 151: 2)
  - Uganda: Non-Africans, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 151: 3)
  - Uganda, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 151: 4)
  - Protection: human rights, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 151: 5)
  - Protection: Zimbabwe, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 151: 6)
  - Zimbabwe: ethnic relations, 1981 (Box-folder 151: 7)
  - Financial guarantees: Rhodesia, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 151: 8)
  - KANU, 1965-1976 (Box-folder 151: 9)
  - Kenya, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 151: 10)
  - Uganda, 1973 (Box-folder 151: 11)
  - Miscellaneous Africa, 1955-1980 (Box-folder 151: 12)
- Printed matter, 1959-1977
  - Serial issues, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 152: 1-2)
  - Clippings, 1977 (Box-folder 152: 3)
  - Atlas, 1959 (Box-folder 152: 4)